https://vancouverpolicemuseum.ca/privacypolicy/

The Vancouver Police Museum | Privacy Policy
Hours: Thurs-Sat 10 am-5 pm | Sun, noon-5 pm | Closed on Stat Holidays
VisitVisiting During COVID-19ExhibitsEventsEducationToursPressBlogRentalsAbout/ContactDonateVolunteerPrivacy Policy Vancouver Police Museum > Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyThe Vancouver Police Museum is committed to protecting your privacy, security and safety. In our Privacy Policy, you will learn how we collect and use visitor data via our website and other physical and digital means in accordance with the BC Personal Information and Privacy Act.Your InformationFirst and foremost, we will never sell, hand over or license your information to third-party vendors for any reason whatsoever. The information we collect is for the benefit of ensuring the Vancouver Police Museum’s operations and viability. It allows us to pursue exhibits, events, education programs, tours and other museum-related activities that are interesting to our visitors and online and mobile users. As a not-for-profit institution, we do not engage in any activities that merchandise your personal information or privacy to third-party vendors in any way. We collect information purely for our own marketing purposes so we can ensure the livelihood of our museum and staff.CookiesAs with most websites, we collect cookies through the website browser that you use. We use cookies to gather certain information about our users, such as language, region, browser type and other segments as deemed appropriate by Google Analytics—our current data collection platform. This information is used to further enhance visitor experiences in the brick and mortar museum and online via our website and social media channels. Facebook, Instagram, Google MyBusiness and Twitter have their own privacy policies that clarify their use and collection of data, and our social media channels abide by their rules using their proprietary business tools, such as Facebook Business and Instagram Business. You may opt-out of cookies procedures by disabling cookies on your web browser. You may also opt-out of social media cookie policies on each individual social media platform.PhotosWe use photos from our events and programs only with your consent. Either we display a notice in our building about photography or video rights, or we issue a statement in an official contract agreement, such as with our education programs. We are not responsible for individual visitors who take photos and post them for their own purposes on social media or other online platforms. Should you find a photo with your image, and you wish it not to be used, please contact us directly and we will remove it. All photos are used for promotional purposes only and are never sold or licensed for profit.EmailWe collect email addresses through registration to our programs, events and newsletter.These email addresses are only used for outreach purposes, whereby we send patrons, visitors and users information about upcoming events, programs, tours, exhibits, deals, promotions and more. We never give email addresses and associated information to third-party vendors for profit. You may opt-out of receiving emails from us by clicking unsubscribe in the footer of any email. Technology PlatformsOur technology platforms, such as Constant Contact, WordPress, Eventbrite, Paypal, Moneris and Google Forms, have access to visitor and user information so they can serve us as a business or payment platform. Each has exceptional security and safety measures to protect your information, but we are not responsible for security breaches to their technology.Questions?If you have questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at 604.665.3346 or info@vancouverpolicemuseum.ca.  ShareAbout   The Vancouver Police Museum & Archives is an independent museum run by the Vancouver Police Historical Society, a registered charity. The Museum’s foundations began in celebration of the Vancouver Police Department’s centennial anniversary in 1986 and have since expanded beyond the blue lens of local law enforcement to include the history of the Vancouver Coroner’s Services and the historic City Analyst Laboratory that houses the museum.NavigationVisitVisiting During COVID-19ExhibitsEventsEducationCanuel ScholarshipToursCollectionsAbout/ContactDonatePressBlogVolunteerPrivacy PolicyRecent Tweets
Fingerprinting can get a little difficult when you don't have hands. Luckily, if you are a Police Dog, then there's… https://t.co/qELUrWJGId
3 months ago
Who says uniforms can’t be fashionable? Check out V.P.D. Constable Haynes modelling a new uniform in the summer of… https://t.co/UAReR2omyS
3 months ago
How many officers can you count?? We're glad the Drill Team doesn't do such risky stunts anymore! https://t.co/q6PXvic7kn
4 months ago
Follow @policemuseum
Location: 240 East Cordova Street, Vancouver, BC, 604-665-3346 All Rights Reserved
×Your ticket for the: Privacy Policy
TitlePrivacy Policy CAD
Close Print
